

BOYD Stacken

MARKETING | SALES

CONTACT

- (C) (715) 559-9677
- 766 Magoo Rd. Hudson, WI 54016

PRO SKILLS

- Innovative Thinking
- Effective Communicator
- · Analytical & Results Driven
- · Collaborative & Independent
- · Customer-first Perspective
- · Online Reputation Management
 - CRM Management
- · Email & Direct Mail Marketing
- Adobe Lightroom, Illustrator & Photoshop
 - SEO & Content Optimization

ABOUT ME

Experienced Marketing & Sales Professional driven to be a part of a market-leading organization that stands behind their products and services while delivering a custom-er-first experience. With hands-on integration of marketing, sales, customer reputation management, and communication, I've had the opportunity to be a part of success and want to share that with a company while utilizing my full potential. I believe my past experiences and skill sets can contribute to the company's enduring success.

EDUCATION

2012 - 2016

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS BACHELOR OF SCIENCE | COMMUNICATION STUDIES

University of Wisconsin - River Falls

WORK EXPERIENCE

REGIONAL MARKETING MANAGER SERVICE SALES MANAGER

N8232 945th St. River Falls, WI

Green Oasis | May 2016 - Current

- Grow customer count in all services & monitor new sales and cancel rates regularly
- Train and manage inside/outside service sales staff
- · Create and manage and track inside sales campaigns
- Develop effective sales methods for field employees
- Monitor and Implement up-sell opportunities using automated systems & processes
- Develop loyalty programs to assist in retaining customers
- Enhance and manage online reviews to positively reflect company reputation
- Implement efficient communication models to strengthen customers' experiences
- \bullet Provide valuable & relevant content to increase credibility and client engagement
- Design and plan email & direct mail campaigns for sales & educational purposes
 Showcase projects & community involvement through Social Media Platforms
- Cross marketing services to existing customers
- Trade show coordination and execution to establish new leads & potential clients
- · Update website content to improve the user experience and utilize for SEO ranking
- Execute sweepstakes, contests, & sponsorships to engage with local communities
- Utilize budgets efficiently with outside vendors and through internal strategies

SALES & MARKETING INTERN

N8232 945th St. River Falls, WI

Green Oasis | Sept. 2015 - May 2016

- Educated customers regarding benefits and features of our service programs
- Sold over \$30,000 in lawn care, irrigation and pest control sales
- Prospered and critiqued sales scripting and email marketing campaigns
- · Performed account acquisition and processed transactions in CRM platform
- •Created and presented daily reports in a timely manner